Contact

4974 Myers Road Columbus, Ohio 43232 7576751585 (Mobile) renalbeginnings@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/carlajames-99b52553 (LinkedIn) www.cmjames.organogold.com/r/ US (Personal)

Top Skills

Network Marketing Entrepreneurship Small Business

Carla James

Independent Nurse Provider

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Organo Gold is on a mission, spreading the knowledge of Ganoderma to the four corners of the world. By using the cost effective network distribution system to deliver these Ganoderma products, more of every dollar is shared with our growing Organo Gold family world-wide.

Think about your future. Where will you and your family be in 5 years from right now? You may know where you want to be, but do you know how you are going to get there? Do you have a plan? Now more than ever it's up to you to define your future. That's where Organo Gold comes into the picture.

Organo Gold is a global family that is growing and thriving every day. A family that is caring and compassionate and believes that the knowledge of Ganoderma should be in the hands of people worldwide. It's a family that cares about you.

Experience

Millenia Medical Staffing
Travel Nurse
August 2015 - Present (4 years 11 months)
Houston, Texas Area

Ohio Home Care Program Independent Nurse Provider October 2014 - Present (5 years 9 months) Columbus, Ohio Area

Providing home care services to Medicaid patients in the Columbus, Ohio area.

McNaughten Pointe Skilled Nursing and Rehab Facility LPN Charge Nurse July 2014 - Present (6 years)

- Charge Nurse for 150 bed unit
- Giving medication as prescribed by a physician
- Taking vital signs, such as blood pressure, temperature, and weight
- Basic wound care including cleaning and bandaging injured areas
- Giving injections of medication
- Immunizations
- · Taking medical histories
- Entering information into computer systems
- Managing IVs
- Ensuring patients and their families understand release instructions
- Supervising CNAs (Certified Nursing Assistants)
- · Monitoring fluid and food intake and output
- · Moving patients safely

Vision Home Health Care, LLC Nurse May 2014 - Present (6 years 2 months)

National Church Residences LPN Lead May 2014 - Present (6 years 2 months)

- Duties include administering medications to clients attending the adult day center, glucose check, vital signs, wound care and assessment, care plans. Monitors client's physical, social and emotional status; evaluates symptoms, reactions, progress. Provides continuity of care.
- Insures the availability and proper maintenance of medical supplies and equipment needed in the center.
- Performs nursing evaluations on all clients; plans and provides care and education to meet individual client's health needs. This involves recording all pertinent health data and being responsible for the compilation and maintenance of client care plans and records.
- Acts as a liaison between the client, caregiver, physician, and other health care providers involved in the client's care. Works in concert with the social worker when dealing with client/caregiver issues.
- Is responsible for notifying family and/or physician appropriately as changes in the client's health needs or condition occur.
- Administers all medications and treatments as ordered by the client's physician and documents the same.

Organo Gold

Independent Distributor
April 2012 - Present (8 years 3 months)

Distributor of organic gourmet tea and coffee.

Nationwide Childrens Hospital Patient Care Assistant 2006 - 2013 (7 years)

Renal Beginnings Foundation

Founder

January 2000 - December 2006 (7 years)

Founder

New Orleans Nephrology Associates

Working Manager

January 1997 - August 2005 (8 years 8 months)

Established nephrology practice

Turned profit first year in business

Implemented anemia clinic and clinical research protocols increasing profitability of practice

Ochsner Clinics

Project Leader, Renal Beginnings Foundation January 1997 - January 2003 (6 years 1 month)

Established a program to identify and educate individuals at risk for chronic kidney disease

Developed marketing material, web site to promote program

Traveled to national meetings speaking on programs accomplishments

Education

Hondros College of Nursing

Diploma, Practical Nursing, Vocational Nursing and Nursing

Assistants · (2013 - 2014)

University of Phoenix